Financiero.
All of
A selfless public servant,
Vice Admiral T-Borne was beloved
by Marines and citizens alike.
His sudden death shocked the world.
The Navy announced that he died in the
line of duty, but provided no details.
Have they found a killer yet?
I'm not sure.
But we've been keeping an eye on the family,
and they seem to be living comfortably.
Of course they are.
What a mess.
Never imagined I'd live in a world
where marines are murdered by civilians.
Pirates aren't the only
ones who want money.
This was inevitable from the
moment we received bounties.
T-Bone was killed in Papa Kingdom, where
over a thousand people starve every year.
Certainly no excuse, but poverty can
drive even the sanest men to madness.
If this was all the genius Jester's
plan, then we've underestimated him.
How can we expect our
men to risk their lives
to save citizens who
are out for their blood?
We need to destroy Cross Guild soon.
Morale is more essential than you'd think.
A seed of doubt can
become a deadly poison.
Oh, Hina!
Have you seen Garp today?
I've got some new crackers
I want him to try.
Yeah, about that.
He set up a while ago.
He said he was going to rescue Kobe.
I think he may have taken
some members of S .W .O .R .D.
with him, which means
Kuchiku's probably there.
What?
You're saying they went to Fuller land?
So you survived your long
journey across the sea? Yes, sir.
Excellent work!
The whole criminal world
is singing your praises.
Three cheers for you, our evil star!
I heard the news, sir.
That you sent the money to my family.
Thank you.
I owe you my life.
Think nothing of it.
You single-handedly killed a
vice-admiral in cold blood.
Such plenty deserves the reward.
From what I hear, those poor Marines
still haven't gotten over it.
You'd better hope that
they don't find you.
They'll chop your pretty head off.
Oh, no, I could never go
back home to my family again.
It's better than letting
them starve to death.
Don't worry, pal.
Once you join my crew, you'll
have a whole new family.
Join your crew?
Welcome to the team, pal!
No, I could never.
You don't get it, do you?
Our chairman ain't just a
pirate, he's an emperor.
Most pirates don't even get to look at
the man, let alone sail by his side.
And yet there he is, the real
deal, the bonafide buggy! Yeah!
Bonafide!
Bonafide buggy!
I like that it's catchy.
Excuse me, Chairman Bonafide buggy!
My thighs are super shapely!
I have good news, sir!
Cross-Killed's ship is all done!
Don't worry about the ship.
I got a team of crews that'll
whip up a real masterpiece!
Like me! That's why!
That's right!
We're crazy about you!
This is the King of Ships!
Do you love it or what?
We're so good at this!
This is how I'm done!
Hey, let it better not be our ship.
Surely you don't expect me to sail
on that ridiculous-looking thing.
Meeting room, now.
It's not my feet!
Crossgill's public reception
has been excellent.
Now that our name's out there, the Navy
will wake up to the threat that we pose.
Please, kill me.
I'm begging you.
It hurts.
Our goal is to create a utopia,
a military nation that won't bow to
the government or to anyone else.
And for that, only one thing is necessary.
An overwhelming amount of strength.
This is not the life I
envisioned for myself.
I'm in hell.
But in order to acquire the
strength we need, first we...
Need wealth, fame, and power? Huh?
Sorry, I got a bit carried away.
Shut your mouth.
Screw this!
If you want to shut me up that
bad, just kill me already!
But, I'll tell you one last thing!
These goals you're chasing are small-time!
How can you call yourself a
pirate thinking like that?
What's this? Desperation.
You heard right.
When he finally decided it
was time to make his move.
He and I both rode on Roger's
ship back in his prime,
but for one reason or another, we
didn't make it to Laugh Tale in the end.
When you took to the sea,
you had a dream too, right?
Honestly, when I saw how much potential
Shanks had back then, I gave up my dream.
I let it die!
I haven't forgotten what you said, Shanks!
You said you'd make it to Laugh
Tale on your ship! You swore!
Yeah, but I changed my mind.
That's not what I want
to fight for right now.
I'll still be a pirate, though.
I thought you were
better than that, Shanks.
I thought you'd be the one leading the
charge for the next generation of pirates.
Come with me, Buggy.
You'll see.
You think I want to work for you
after that crap he's just told me?
You're a damn coward!
Captain Roger wanted you
to follow in his footsteps.
Can't you see that?
I lost my treasure map because of you!
I'm sure you want to blow that off like you
do everything else, but I'm still angry!
In fact, from now on, you're my enemy!
Now he suddenly changes his mind?
After all this time, to hell with him!
Even if I just got lucky, I
am an emperor, same as him!
I want to be king!
The king of the pirates!
Well, Gene has power, too!
We just have to find it!
Roger's treasure is waiting for us!
That's enough out of you!
Seems your new title is giving
you delusions of grandeur.
Should we beat some more sense into you?
Did you honestly think your
insipid speech would work on us?
Piracy is a business,
not some little game.
You think you can be king without a plan?
Red hair, black beard, and Straw Hat.
Those are the enemies
we would have to face.
Yeah, but we can outsmart them!
A treasure hunt is a race, not a war!
You made fun of my speech!
I'll show you how inspirational I can be!
Why do you think pirates
took to the sea to chase
dreams greater than they
never dared to imagine?
Listen up, men!
Don't you even think about it.
Come on, tell me!
What dream drove you to the sea?
In our world, you could
die before you know it.
Aren't your souls crying out for
something that's worth fighting for?
He's right!
I can feel it!
My lost passion is coming back to life!
Only a coward would be
satisfied for the status quo.
If you have a dream, then chase
it with all your strength!
I've got your back.
There's no need to fear.
There's only one goal for us now.
The One Piece!
What?
I can see the ship.
You okay, pal? Just breathe.
We're almost there.
Keep it together.
Hey, Ahiru! Whatcha think? A good ship?
Or a bad ship? Is it a
friend? Enemy? Who? What? How?
You know, I've been faking fears.
Quiet, I need to focus.
Warp, flag, punk.
Say, would you care to make a bet?
On what sort of ship that is, I mean.
I wager it's an enemy.
Are you in?
Yeah, okay.
Woosh.
You're on, my friend.
I'll bet that's up, oh shit.
How's a million sound?
Wado?
A million?
Dragon! Evil!
It's Sabo!
He finally came home to us!
Hee-haw!
That's our boy!
Why, I wasn't worried one bit!
I missed him so much!
Sabo!
Samu!
Hey guys, it's been a while.
We're not the best of all!
Damn you, Geron!
I know you cheated somehow!
I won't give you one berry!
Sorry, pal, but I won
the bet fair and square.
What is that?
Are you using a telescope?
I don't know.
Lying fraud!
Open your mouth!
What?
Welcome back.
I was just about to shoot you.
Well, I'm glad you didn't, Ahiru.
Were you worried about me? Maybe. Sabo!
I'm so happy you're safe!
Hey, thanks, Ushiano.
Nice to see you.
You little scamp!
Don't you know it's rude
to keep a queen waiting?
We were all in a stew waiting for news!
It's been quite the journey.
Well, stop teasing and spill the tea!
This ship is from Lulusia.
The kingdom that just
vanished into thin air?
Yeah.
I'll explain things later.
For now, we should find
them a place to rest.
Hey, Sabo!
How dare you go radio silence on us!
I'm sorry, but I did have a choice!
I couldn't get an encrypted
transponder snail.
They were gonna tap the line.
I couldn't risk talking any longer.
But you guys did hear me give
the indirect call signal, right?
The three knocks?
I was out of La Lucia, perfectly safe.
All right!
But don't ever make me
worry like that again, okay?
Okay, sorry.
Samo!
You scared us half to death!
Why do you men always have to leave?
Hi, Morley.
If you ever break my heart
like that again, I'll...
I'll...
I can't stay bad at you.
I'm so glad you're back.
Nice to see you again.
Hello.
I remember you.
You're the chumps from the Lucia.
I'm sorry you lost your home.
I heard you want to join the Revolutionary
Army? Yes, ma 'am! We're ready!
Not yet, you're not.
Get some rest first.
Sort out your feelings.
I heard what happened with Kuma.
I'm sorry.
It seems we've wasted your time.
If they program Kuma to return
to Marie Joie automatically,
our efforts may have been
futile from the start. Maybe so.
I know this is hard on you two.
More than anyone else.
Listen, getting back to business, you can't
even share your news with the captains.
No, it's too dangerous.
This is something I can
only share with you.
What is it?
The truth about what
happened at Morishois.
I'm going to tell you everything
about what I saw that day.
The day of the reverie.
We managed to accomplish
all of our missions.
There were three general objectives.
We declared war on the Celestial
Dragons by destroying their symbol.
Then we set as many of their slaves free
as we could, including Kuma, of course.
And then, we destroyed the
food reserves in Mariejoie.
What results have you seen?
Well, we've caught the world's
attention, which was the point.
The Navy forces were busy chasing you,
so things worked out conveniently.
In short,
12 different countries revolted
against the government,
with our encouragement, that is.
It wasn't flawless, of course, but
eight of the revolts were successful.
The newspapers called it
the Eight Nation Revolution,
though I suppose seven would be more
accurate now that the Lucia has vanished.
One detail wasn't reported.
Our forces have been
starving out the enemy.
Seven nations have declined
to pay their heavenly tributes
and have stopped exporting
resources to the government.
Yes, not to mention we've been attacking
government shipments all over the world!
Completely cutting off
Marie Joie's supplies.
We were warned the capital
would be impenetrable
because it's so high above sea level.
But who cares of opposition
when we've got attrition?
Let them hide!
They won't last a week
without money or food!
I think we'll see a response soon.
Given our enemy, yes.
The nobles are used to getting
what they want when they want it.
For those who have known nothing but
luxury, this will be pure torment.
They're not the sort of people who will
sit back and endure an insult like this.
They're going to dispatch
the holy knights.
That's when the real battle begins.
Sabo! No!
Flame Emperor Boy!
You are at the top of the
government's hit list now!
Can we please drop the nickname?
It's ridiculous.
Like it or not, it's the
name that made you an icon.
I know you didn't kill them,
but being framed for Cobra's murder has
made you a hero to rebels worldwide.
And many of those rebels hold
a common view that anyone
who was involved with the
world government must be evil.
Of course, the truth
isn't black and white.
Even if the system is rotten, there are
good kings alongside all the tyrants.
King Cobra of Alabasta was well-liked and
had a reputation as a kind and wise ruler.
But reputations can be
deceiving sometimes.
I agree.
Cobra was a victim.
And his death was a tragedy.
But if it fueled the rebellion,
then it was necessary.
You've got conviction.
In that case, tell us everything!
I want the truth!
What happened here?
We all cried together, trying
to make sense of what we heard.
But we never lost our faith in you.
This is a tale from over a month ago.
Nobles from all over the
world gathered in the holy
land of Marichois for the
council known as the Reverie.
This is an emergency!
Intruders have infiltrated
the land of the gods!
All citizens, evacuating Median lands!
A full-blown house explorer!
Do something, you imbeciles!
Our lives are in danger! Yeah!
All revolutionary army captains have
been identified on the premises!
Those bastards!
Burning down our symbol is
surely a crime worthy of death,
but burning our food
adds insult to injury.
They're jealous of us
because they're all poor!
When we catch those rats, heads will rule!
You gods will pay dearly
for letting this happen!
Your incompetence will
be the death of you!
We will have all of your heads!
I told you to hurry up!
Move, you lazy mongrel!
Are you really going to
let me burn to death?
Move faster this instant!
That hurts!
I can't believe you're
going to make me walk!
You're not worth the hour you breathe!
You've been terminated, filthy beast.
My gun!
Who in blazes are you?
That's a human life.
Does that mean nothing to you?
Karasu!
Run to the east side of town.
I will. Thank you.
Please, hurry, St. Blooming.
You need to evacuate immediately.
Damn you, Cypher-Pole.
Where were you?
Stop your dallying and
exterminate that vermin.
A revolutionary.
Shoot him!
Come at him.
Just keep firing.
Don't stop till you're sure he's dead!
Damn it for the dead of the switch!
Wait, everyone hold your fire!
What happened to his body?
We killed him, didn't we?
So where the hell is he?
Aversuch!
No!
Run, trash.
Someone help me already!
Please help!
Let us escape too!
We'll die if we stay chained like this!
Don't leave us!
Well, hello!
I'll get those chains for you! Hang tight!
What's happening?
Nobody move, okay?
Here goes!
Laser shooter!
Now run!
We're to the east side of town.
We'll get out of this place together.
Thank you so much, Willie.
You guys can take me later.
Just run for now.
That's a big one, huh?
Lindbergh!
We've got enemies incoming!
Hurry up and through the slays!
No problem!
Something is headed this way.
Something strong.
No!
Oh, no!
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh!
Get back here!
How dare you repulsive
slaves defy my orders!
What is the meaning of this?
Pass, did I make you
trip and fall? A giant!
I'll be taking that.
You'll never point this
nasty thing at people again.
Yoo-hoo, boys, time to get shaken.
Go to the east side of town.
My little friends will be expecting you.
Go!
And be careful! Thank you!
You revolutionaries really piss me off!
You know what it means to
attack the Celestial Dragons.
The punishment for your crimes is death!
You're the temper, don't you, Tree?
Are you all barking no bite?
Shut your mouth, freak!
Why are you destroying the town?
And where the hell is your commander?
Bringing in a third on our date? Really?
You pervert!
No, hell no!
I'm not taking that from you!
Look at what you're wearing!
What?
Are you checking me out?
My goodness!
You're really ugly, aren't you?
If you like me that much, just say so!
Time to die!
You!
Ryo Kukyu!
Now see here!
If we're hurt, I'll have your head!
That's a promise!
Then get your asses out of the way!
I'm fighting here!
Hey, Fujitora!
What the hell are you doing down there?
Ending this, I'm calling a meteor.
Are you out of your mind?
Stop that!
Two admirals if this
wasn't the land of the
gods they would have
turned this place to dust.
They're still making
quite the mess the rebels
aren't backing down even though they're at
a disadvantage if they
have that much confidence
their captains must be terribly fearsome.
Terribly! Yuyoi!
Fine, then.
We'll let the admirals handle things.
Let's move out.
Sabo, have you found
the keys to the callers?
I know where they are, at least.
I should have them soon.
Hey, Lindbergh!
That's you, Sabo? What is it?
Kuma was heading off to
Pangaea Castle. What?
You mean on his own?
I saw him with St.
Rosward and his son, Charlos.
I think they're on their way to finish what
they started in the Mingling Courtyard.
Wait, what?
You're going to be my new pet.
Just wait, my dear.
That means Princess
Shirahoshi is in danger.
They make Kuma do their
dirty work for them.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to let them use him.
Hey, Morley.
Get ready.
Okie Dock.
We'll save Kuma.
No matter what the cost.
Hold on, Dad.
Please return to your room
will you? Leave me alone!
If you must know, I'm
going to ask Garp for help.
We will provide all the
protection you need.
Oh, will you now?
Like you did for Shura Hachi.
You let that happen.
That is on you.
They'll come after her
again and you know it.
Your Majesty, please don't push yourself.
I finally have a chance
to meet the five elders.
It may very well be my last.
Halt!
Only King Cobra has permitted an
audience with the five elders.
What?
Step back, you two.
I won't be long, but I imagine it
would be quite dull to wait here.
Why don't you look after Vivi for me?
She still gets up to mischief.
I can't help but worry about her.